we are focused on where our best
opportunities are the options we have on
growth and distribution on products and
channels and markets and a lot of what
you're going to hear today is about the
discipline that we're using in the our
lens on when we accelerated in a market
when we don't how we allocate capital
when we won't when we pull back
which markets we think have unique
characteristics right now when we look
at our markets the the attributes we've
told you time and again that we think
are key or structural drivers in Asia
that can be the infancy of the market in
the u.s. that can be changes and you
know in the regulatory policy around the
baby boomers options in the UK they're
quite similar nature a large asset
management market where we don't see
natural players emerging to solve what's
a very large consumer demand and the
savings gap so the upside we have in the
market comes from the fact we have the
scale and the establishment of trust
relationships good execution
historically in the markets and there's
a consumer value that we have that again
is ours to defend
we continue to make good progress
through 2017 new business metrics in our
life operations are moving forward and
an asset management we are seeing the
benefit of both sizeable net inflows and
the appreciation in investment markets
across all the group new business flows
are adding to our sizeable stock our
earning drivers are moving forward and
the focus on quality is intact we invest
our capital and new business
opportunities that are of sufficient
scale and exhibit the right
characteristics in terms of quality
return and payback the operating
progress of our businesses to date
continue to demonstrate the key
attributes of the group namely strong
market positioned in the right markets
broad diversification and delivery
across geography product and Channel and
the ability to adapt at pace to new
opportunities and changes in market
conditions
between 2015 and 2030 some 178 million
people will reach working age in Asia
roughly equivalent to the combined
population of the UK France and Italy so
with a current customer base of just 15
million we have plenty of headroom to
grow every month this year we have
recruited on average 15 thousand agents
handled two million customer
interactions and processed nearly
200,000 claims so far in 2017 we have
added over a million new customers with
our annualized customer retention rate
has remained around the 95 percent level
we have a world-class business in the
region with all the right attributes for
success such as scale quality and
leading market positions
we operate in two of the world's largest
investment markets the UK and Europe and
both of which are forecast to grow by
trillions over the next five to ten
years we think this is a really
attractive market for two main reasons
growing demand for our solutions
particularly from transfer of risk to
individuals and the real need for
differentiated investment offerings and
our vision for energy prudential is a
business built around and for the
customer one that is simple and
efficient
digitally enabled
capital light fast-growing and above all
focused on delivery
the principle product that we sell the
variable annuity written with living
benefit guarantees is an incredibly
virtuous product and a product that is
uniquely useful in the environment in
which most pre retiree and immediately
post retiring Americans find themselves
because of our proven track record of
outstanding performance because of our
clear capability in terms of risk
management product pricing product
design because of our highly competent
front-end the job we do in educating
advisors so they sell the product
properly there's no doubt that we
benefit disproportionately
from that rise in the marketplace we are
capable of
benefiting from this retirement crisis
if you if you want to call it that by
delivering strong outcomes to consumers
strong outcomes to shareholders and
doing it all in a compliant way
it's the consistency of key metrics that
that says we're doing what we should do
with the capital and the resources and
the talent and the market footprint we
have we are in the top investment
markets we think for our products and
services in the world in almost all of
them we have market leading positions we
have great teams on the ground with
local execution and I think we're
disciplined and you can demonstrate that
to you on how we allocate capital and
resources to them to produce the highest
return in value for shareholders